<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Tribe</title>
    <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Tribe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://galwaytribe.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tribal Gathering</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/events/tribalgathering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/events/tribalgathering/</guid>
      <description>In August 2023 the Galway Ultimate community, led by members of Tribe, will host a new and exciting high level mixed tournament Tribal Gathering.
Registration is still open. Come and visit one of the most friendly and rapidly developing Ultimate scenes in the world. Home to European champions both at national and club level, Irish Ultimate is in rude health on the field and remains as welcoming as ever off the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>University of Galway</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/ug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/ug/</guid>
      <description>The first ultimate team in Galway was the National University of Ireland, Galway team. Back in 2005 Thomas O’Rourke founded the NUIG Panteras, named after Las Panteras de Xalapa, an Ultimate team from Mexico from whom Thomas learned the sport.
The team grew slowly at first driven on by players like Eoin Wallace, Luke Watson &amp;amp; Paddy Costello. In the early years the team trained on the President’s Lawn in front of the beautiful quadrangle at the heart of the college campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snatch</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/snatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/snatch/</guid>
      <description>Galway&#39;s first club team Snatch was formed in 2011 by Galway and Limerick based players looking to play at a higher level than was possible on their university teams. Galway and Limerick Stalwarts such as Eoin Wallace, Liam Grant, James Moore and Liam Anderson were the driving forces behind the club&amp;rsquo;s formation.
The club debuted in its distincive yellow and black in the Open Division at the All Ireland Ultimate Championships in 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tribe</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/tribe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/tribe/</guid>
      <description>Tribe was established in 2016 and made its debut in the Open Division at Yes But Nau and the Women&amp;rsquo;s Division at Munster Munch that year. Tribe&amp;rsquo;s first outing in the Mixed Division was at Windmill 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Representing Ireland</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/international/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/international/</guid>
      <description>The Galway Ultimate community is proud to have been represented by a large number of Galway-based players on various Irish national teams over the years. Male and female-matching Galway-based players have played at Junior, U23/U24 and Senior levels.
First players to represent Ireland at different levels: Junior
FMP: Eimear O&amp;rsquo;Reilly EYUC 2011 MMP: Barry O Gorman EYUC 2017 U23
FMP: Dorothee Driever World U23 Mixed 2019 MMP: Niall McDermott World U23 Mixed 2012 Senior</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools Ultimate in Galway</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/schools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/schools/</guid>
      <description>Galway ultimate community members have introduced ultimate to a number of city schools over the years including Coláiste Éinde, Coáiste Iognáid, and Calasanctius College.
Galway&amp;rsquo;s first schools team to compete at a tournament was Calasanctius College who competed at the 2016 All Ireland Schools competition. The team was coached by Tribe members Eoin Breen and Cormac Shields who played for Tribe&amp;rsquo;s predecessor Snach at the time. Current Tribe U24 captain Shane Monaghan got his first taste of ultimate on this team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tournaments in Galway</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/events/</guid>
      <description>Galway has a proud of history of hosting tournaments, and tournament parties. In 2023 the inaugural Tribal Gathering will take place, bringing high level mixed-teams from around the globe to the West of Ireland for a weekend of high-level play and higher-level partying.
Galway Open Galway Open was the brainchild of former NUIG captain Liam Grant. The event took place in 2010 and 2011 in Dangan Sportsground on the University fo Galway Campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Basics</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/ultimate/basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/ultimate/basics/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate is a non-contact, self-refereed team sport played with a flying disc. Ultimate brings together elements of soccer, american football, and basketball to create a dynamic, action-packed, high-intensity game that requires a high degree of speed, endurance, skill, and most importantly, teamwork.
A game of ultimate is played by two teams with a flying disc on a pitch with end zones, similar to an american football pitch but narrower. The object of the game is to score by catching a pass in the opponent’s end zone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rules</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/ultimate/rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/ultimate/rules/</guid>
      <description>Ultimate is a non-contact, self-refereed team sport played with a flying disc (or Frisbee™). Two teams of seven players compete on a rectangular pitch. At each end of the pitch there is an end zone. Each team defends one endzone. They score a goal if one of their players catches the disc in the opposite end zone. The player with the disc is called the thrower and may not run with the disc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spirit of the Game</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/ultimate/spirit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/ultimate/spirit/</guid>
      <description>Spirit of the Game is one of the core elements in flying disc sports. It is similar to fair play and sportsmanship, but there is a much higher emphasis put on it in Ultimate and it is one of the defining aspects of the sport. Spirit of the Game places the responsibility of fair play solely on the players by requiring each player to know the rules and make their own calls, without the help of a referee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
