<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>History on Tribe</title>
    <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in History on Tribe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>University of Galway</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/ug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/ug/</guid>
      <description>The first ultimate team in Galway was the Naional University of Ireland, Galway team. Back in 2005 Thomas O’Rourke founded the NUIG Panteras, named after Las Panteras de Xalapa, an Ultimate team from Mexico from whom Thomas learned the sport. Slowly the team grew with support from players like Eoin Wallace, Luke Watson &amp;amp; Paddy Costello. The team trained on ‘the President’s Lawn’ a lovely patch of grass at the heart of the college campus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snatch</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/snatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/snatch/</guid>
      <description>Galway&amp;rsquo;s first club team Snatch was formed in 2011 by Galway &amp;amp; Limerick based players.
The club debuted in the Open Division that year at the All Ireland Ultimate Championships. The club debuted in the Mixed Division at AIUC 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tribe</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/tribe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/tribe/</guid>
      <description>Tribe was established in 2016 and made its debut in the Open Division at Yes But Nau and the Women&amp;rsquo;s Division at Munster Munch that year. Tribe&amp;rsquo;s first outing in the Mixed Division was at Windmill 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Representing Ireland</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/international/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/international/</guid>
      <description>Firsts to represent Ireland at different levels: Junior FMP: Eimear O&amp;rsquo;Reilly EYUC 2011 MMP: Barry O Gorman EYUC Open 2017 U23 FMP: Dorothee Driever World U23 Mixed 2019 MMP: Niall McDermott World U23 Mixed 2012 Senior FMP: Emma O&amp;rsquo;Callaghan EUC 2015 Women&amp;rsquo;s MMP: Liam Grant WCBU 2011 Open International Medals Liam Grant: Silver @ECBU 2015 Mixed Barry O&amp;rsquo;Gorman: Silver @EYUC Open 2017 Zoe Langsdale: Gold @EUC Women&amp;rsquo;s 2019</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools Ultimate in Galway</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/schools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/schools/</guid>
      <description>Galway ulimate community members have introduced ultimate to a number of city schools over the years including Coláiste Éinde, Coáiste Iognáid, and Calasanctius College.
Galway&amp;rsquo;s first schools team to compete at a tournament was Calasanctius College who competed at the 2016 All Ireland Schools competition. The team was coached by Tribe members Eoin Breen and Cormac Shields who played for Tribe&amp;rsquo;s predecessor Snach at the time. Current Tribe U24 captain Shane Monaghan got his first taste of ultimate on this team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tournaments in Galway</title>
      <link>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://galwaytribe.github.io/history/events/</guid>
      <description>Galway Open took place in 2010 and 2011. Galway hosted Indoor Nationals in 2019. NUIG has hosted lots of IVs events over the years in all divisions. Women&amp;rsquo;s Indoors 2020, Mixed Indoors 2018 and Open Indoors 2016 are the most recent for each division I believe. Tribe hosted Smugairle Róin an indoor beginner tournament (twice I think) Galway has hosted an annual charity Christmas hat tournament since 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
